Guide to the Paul Kruger Papers SC1302
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Paul Kruger Papers
1958-1996
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Gust, Kathleen
SC1302
3 Linear Feet
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Kathleen Gust, 2016.
Biographical / Historical
Paul Kruger was Professor of Civil Engineering at Stanford.
Scope and Contents
Collection contains files, photographs, and reports relating to Kruger's civil engineering research.
Nuclear engineering; Energy policy.; Gust, Kathleen
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2017-011
  - Figures, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cabriolet, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Milo D. Nordyke, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Animated Chimney Formation, 1971-4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Harbor Excavation, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Marvel, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Plowshare photographs, detonations, 1972-7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Kruger, Warren, Honeyman Radon as An Internal Tracer In Geothermal Reservoirs, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1967-10 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Plowshare material, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Plowshare photographs, applications, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Plowshare photographs, technology, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1974-6-18 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - JGEA Annual Report, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Online Ready Reference Questions, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Test Reports, 1964-1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Photographs, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Volume, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Nevada Test Site, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Progress report No. 3, 1979-4-1-1979-6-30 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Progress report No. 5, 1980-1-1-1980-3-31 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Slides, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Clippings, 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Radiotracker Determination of Hydraulic Residence Time, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Republica de Venezuela, 1972-11-27 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - UC Davis, 1964-4-21-1964-4-23 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Nuclear Methods in Meteorology and Hydrology, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - The Energy Outlook, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 1958-1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Progress Report, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Abstracts CACR, 1969-9-8-1969-9-13 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - CACR Symposium Abstracts, 1965-8-18-1965-8-25 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - 1958-1972 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Advisees (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Draft charge to working group - Budget Equilibrium (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - DAPER (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Equilibrium/Watershed (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Finance liaison team (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Fredrickson (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Freelen (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Chris Golde (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Holloway (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - INEL (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Libraries IR - Report to liaison, 1991 Sep (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Liaison meetings (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Liaison team (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Oscar Manley - Dept. of Energy (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - MHD equipment (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Office of Technology Licensing (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Quals, 1991 Apr (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Research assistantships (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Task force on research and scholarship (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Steve Simpson (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Mike Smith (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - SSRL draft report, 1992 Feb (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Trustee Subcom. On Budget and Planning (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Argonne slides (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Argonne, 1992 May (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Bochum viewgraphs (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Word 4.0 and vugraphs - Diamond Days (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Tim Warner, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Zare (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Kruger - Nonequilibrium effects (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Kruger, 1992 Sep 29 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Pig exam (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Pending (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Diamond Films (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Educom (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - EPRI (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Gaseous Electronics Conf., 1991 Oct (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Steve Girshick (Univ. of Minn) (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - INEL/MIT meeting, 1990 Jul (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Italy (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Matt Gordon (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Gordon Research Conference, 1992 Aug 10-14 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Gordon Research Conference, 1992 Jun (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Gordon Conference, 1990 Aug (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - ME 13 - Introductory Fluid Mechanics (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - ME 262A, 1992 Autumn (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - ME 262A TV students, 1992 Autumn (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Homework (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - ME 262A, 1991 Autumn (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Final (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Handouts ME262A, 1989 Autumn (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Kruger - ME 33 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - ME 262A (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - ME 262, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - ME 262, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - ME 262A (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Campus Report Special budget issue, 1991 Sep 19 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Cab/ Com./Budgetary strategic planning CC/BSP (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - CC-BSP task forces (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - CC/BSP retreat, 1991 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - ME 262 A - handouts, 1990 Autumn (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - CC/BSP Budget strategic planning group (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Faculty Senate, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Senate talks, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Steering committee, 1991 May 22 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Senate review - H S (Box 2, Folder 66)